<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MindfulnessProjectQuotesPictures</string>
    <string name="start_screen_welcome">Welcome to the Mindfulness Project!</string>
    <string name="start_screen_button">Get Started</string>


    <string name="choose_options_title">What do you want to do?</string>
    <string name="meditation_button_text">Meditation Timer</string>
    <string name="quotes_button_text">Quotes</string>

    
    <!--QUOTES-->
    <string name="unnamed_quote_1">It's good to have places of comfort so we can go into those places to help us unwind and recharge.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_2">The best way to become a billionaire is to help a billion people.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_3">The fishermen know that the sea is dangerous and the storm terrible, but they have never found these dangers sufficient reason for remaining ashore.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_4">Every man is happy until happiness is suddenly a goal.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_5">Nothing fails like success</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_6">I believe that when things are bad I can change them.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_7">When you are casual about life you will end up a casualty.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_8">There is a difference between failure and being a failure.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_9">Don't be stuck. Keep moving.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_10">Destiny is not a matter of chance; it's a matter of choice. It is not a thing to be waited for; it is a thing to be achieved.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_11">Change is never a matter of ability, it's a matter of motivation.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_12">Before you ask something of someone else, ask everything of yourself.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_13">The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_14">A person can change his future by merely changing his attitude.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_15">Nothing is real that is not eternal.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_16">Don't be yourself, be your best self.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_17">You only live once, but if you work it right, once is enough.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_18">Only those who will risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_19">The world is against me, it wouldn't be fair otherwise</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_20">The loser and the winner both fail, the winner gets back up and does it again.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_21">Every problem, every challenge that you have, is ultimately an opportunity.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_22">Whether you think you can or think you can't, you're right</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_23">Feel fear and do it anyway.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_24">Well-makers lead the water(wherever they like); fletchers bend the arrow; carpenters bend a log of wood; wise people fashion themselves.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_25">Imagination is more powerful than knowledge.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_26">To accomplish great things, we must not only act, but also dream; not only plan, but also believe.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_27">Sometimes you will never know the value of a moment until it is a memory.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_28">If you limit your choices to what seems possible or reasonable, you disconnect yourself from what you truly want and all that is left is compromise.</string>



</resources>
