<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MindfulnessProjectQuotesPictures</string>
    <string name="start_screen_welcome">Welcome to the Mindfulness Project!</string>
    <string name="start_screen_button">Get Started</string>


    <string name="choose_options_title">What do you want to do?</string>
    <string name="meditation_button_text">Meditation Timer</string>
    <string name="quotes_button_text">Quotes</string>

    <string name="get_quote_button_text">Generate random quote!</string>


    <!--QUOTES-->

    <!--changed all lowercase b's to capital to match capture it font-->
    <string-array name="quote_list">
        <item>It\'s good to have places of comfort so we can go into those places to help us unwind and recharge.</item>
        <item>The Best way to Become a Billionaire is to help a Billion people.</item>
        <item>The fishermen know that the sea is dangerous and the storm terriBle, But they have never found these dangers sufficient reason for remaining ashore.</item>
        <item>Every man is happy until happiness is suddenly a goal.</item>
        <item>Nothing fails like success</item>
        <item>I Believe that when things are Bad I can change them.</item>
        <item>When you are casual aBout life you will end up a casualty.</item>
        <item>There is a difference Between failure and Being a failure.</item>
        <item>Don\'t Be stuck. Keep moving.</item>
        <item>Destiny is not a matter of chance; it\'s a matter of choice. It is not a thing to Be waited for; it is a thing to Be achieved.</item>
        <item>Change is never a matter of aBility, it\'s a matter of motivation.</item>
        <item>Before you ask something of someone else, ask everything of yourself.</item>
        <item>The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do.</item>
        <item>A person can change his future By merely changing his attitude.</item>
        <item>Nothing is real that is not eternal.</item>
        <item>Don\'t Be yourself, Be your Best self.</item>
        <item>You only live once, But if you work it right, once is enough.</item>
        <item>Only those who will risk going too far can possiBly find out how far one can go.</item>
        <item>The world is against me, it wouldn\'t Be fair otherwise</item>
        <item>The loser and the winner Both fail, the winner gets Back up and does it again.</item>
        <item>Every proBlem, every challenge that you have, is ultimately an opportunity.</item>
        <item>Whether you think you can or think you can\'t, you\'re right</item>
        <item>Feel fear and do it anyway.</item>
        <item>Well-makers lead the water(wherever they like); fletchers Bend the arrow; carpenters Bend a log of wood; wise people fashion themselves.</item>
        <item>Imagination is more powerful than knowledge.</item>
        <item>To accomplish great things, we must not only act, But also dream; not only plan, But also Believe.</item>
        <item>Sometimes you will never know the value of a moment until it is a memory.</item>
        <item>If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles. If you know yourself but not the enemy, for every victory gained you will also suffer a defeat. If you know neither the enemy nor yourself, you will succumb in every battle.</item>
        <item>We don’t rise to the level of our expectations – we fall to the level of our training</item>
        <item>You have to know what you’re aiming for before it is even worth bothering with the process of preparing the bow, nocking the arrow and letting go.</item>
        <item>It\'s not about how much you practice. It\'s about how much your mind is present when practicing.</item>
        <item>One of the key differences between rich people and everyone else is that rich people plan before they need to plan.</item>
        <item>Any business arrangement that is not profitable to the other person will, in the end, prove unprofitable to you. The bargain that yields mutual satisfaction is the only one that is apt to be repeated.” </item>
        <item>What am I not smart enough to ask you that I should?</item>
        <item>The first objective of the coach and players should be a complete mastery of the individual fundamentals. The second objective is the integration of these individuals into a team.</item>
        <item>In (high pressure/stressful) situations, talent is not the most sought-after characteristic. Grace and poise are, because these two attributes precede the opportunity to deploy any other skill.</item>
        <item>You don’t need to be an expert…but if you aren\'t, you must recognize your limitations and follow a course certain to work reasonably well.</item>
        <item>Omniscience isn\'t necessary; you only need to understand the actions you undertake.</item>
        <item>If a company is relying on patents, it’s in a weak position. They\'re not innovating fast enough. You want to be innovating so fast that you invalidate your prior patents.</item>
        <item>Many a false step was made by standing still.</item>
        <item>Action may not always bring happiness, but there is no happiness without action.</item>
        <item>Don\'t be too timid and squeamish about your actions. All life is an experiment. The more experiments you make, the better.</item>
        <item>Nobody can give you freedom. Nobody can give you equality or justice or anything. If you\'re a man, you take it.</item>
        <item>The secret to happiness is freedom. And the secret to freedom is courage</item>
        <item>Things may come to those who wait…but only the things left by those who hustle.</item>
        <item>It\'s a funny thing about life: if you refuse to accept anything but the best, you very often get it.</item>
        <item>The purpose of life is to be defeated by greater and greater things.</item>
        <item>Entrepreneurship is living a few years of your life like most people won’t so you can spend the rest of your life like most people can’t.</item>
        <item>If you limit your choices to what seems possiBle or reasonaBle, you disconnect yourself from what you truly want and all that is left is compromise.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="unnamed_quote_1">It\'s good to have places of comfort so we can go into those places to help us unwind and recharge.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_2">The best way to become a billionaire is to help a billion people.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_3">The fishermen know that the sea is dangerous and the storm terrible, but they have never found these dangers sufficient reason for remaining ashore.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_4">Every man is happy until happiness is suddenly a goal.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_5">Nothing fails like success</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_6">I believe that when things are bad I can change them.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_7">When you are casual about life you will end up a casualty.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_8">There is a difference between failure and being a failure.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_9">Don\'t be stuck. Keep moving.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_10">Destiny is not a matter of chance; it\'s a matter of choice. It is not a thing to be waited for; it is a thing to be achieved.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_11">Change is never a matter of ability, it\'s a matter of motivation.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_12">Before you ask something of someone else, ask everything of yourself.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_13">The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_14">A person can change his future by merely changing his attitude.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_15">Nothing is real that is not eternal.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_16">Don\'t be yourself, be your best self.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_17">You only live once, but if you work it right, once is enough.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_18">Only those who will risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_19">The world is against me, it wouldn\'t be fair otherwise</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_20">The loser and the winner both fail, the winner gets back up and does it again.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_21">Every problem, every challenge that you have, is ultimately an opportunity.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_22">Whether you think you can or think you can\'t, you\'re right</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_23">Feel fear and do it anyway.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_24">Well-makers lead the water(wherever they like); fletchers bend the arrow; carpenters bend a log of wood; wise people fashion themselves.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_25">Imagination is more powerful than knowledge.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_26">To accomplish great things, we must not only act, but also dream; not only plan, but also believe.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_27">Sometimes you will never know the value of a moment until it is a memory.</string>
    <string name="unnamed_quote_28">If you limit your choices to what seems possible or reasonable, you disconnect yourself from what you truly want and all that is left is compromise.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
